<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-12-30T13:37:24-08:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Celeste Starlite’s Website</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><author><name>CelesteStarlite</name><email>celestestarlite@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">poem</title><link href="/poem/2020/12/30/Poems.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="poem" /><published>2020-12-30T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-12-30T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>/poem/2020/12/30/Poems</id><content type="html" xml:base="/poem/2020/12/30/Poems.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;snakes-in-the-shower&quot;&gt;Snakes in the Shower&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turning on the shower
Warm water spilling out onto the floor
A lengthy sigh escapes into the scalding steam.
In rhythmic tapping of drops on my back
My eyes softly close as steam encircles me,
And I sink to the floor underneath the water stream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sitting in the shower
With water rolling down my skin
My wet hair drops down like snakes on my head.
First one, then two, then the whole family
My shaky exhale stumbles out into the air
As my cold, dormant heart fills up with dread.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sighing in the shower
As my snake family begins to speak
All the words that I find I’m afraid of.
First one, then two, the the whole family
Each spitting out scalding insults I try to escape from
As tears stream out like the warm water above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crying in the shower
The snakes screaming louder
My thoughts starting to whirl and my mind beginning to swirl
“You’ll never be as good as him”
“Your choices will never get you anywhere”
“The people you trust will betray one once more”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They wanted a boy, not a girl”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turning off the shower
Snakes spitting out their last drops of water
I take my towel and rub the tears from my eyes.
As I stand before the mirror
And comb my wet hair
I say goodbye to my snake family of lies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>CelesteStarlite</name><email>celestestarlite@gmail.com</email></author><category term="poem" /><summary type="html">Snakes in the Shower</summary></entry></feed>