<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-12-30T19:12:35-08:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Celeste Starlite’s Website</title><subtitle>This is Celeste's (that's me!) personal little website filled with stories and adventures from her time on the internet.
</subtitle><author><name>CelesteStarlite</name></author><entry><title type="html">Poems from 2020</title><link href="/poetry/2020/12/30/2020poems.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Poems from 2020" /><published>2020-12-30T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-12-30T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>/poetry/2020/12/30/2020poems</id><content type="html" xml:base="/poetry/2020/12/30/2020poems.html">&lt;h4 id=&quot;october-29th-2020&quot;&gt;October 29th, 2020&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;snakes-in-the-shower&quot;&gt;Snakes in the Shower&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A poem about negative voices&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turning on the shower&lt;br /&gt;
Warm water spilling out onto the floor&lt;br /&gt;
A lengthy sigh escapes into the scalding steam.&lt;br /&gt;
In rhythmic tapping of drops on my back&lt;br /&gt;
My eyes softly close as steam encircles me,&lt;br /&gt;
And I sink to the floor underneath the water stream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sitting in the shower&lt;br /&gt;
With water rolling down my skin&lt;br /&gt;
My wet hair drops down like snakes on my head.&lt;br /&gt;
First one, then two, then the whole family&lt;br /&gt;
My shaky exhale stumbles out into the air&lt;br /&gt;
As my cold, dormant heart fills up with dread.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sighing in the shower&lt;br /&gt;
As my snake family begins to speak&lt;br /&gt;
All the words that I find I’m afraid of.&lt;br /&gt;
First one, then two, the the whole family&lt;br /&gt;
Each spitting out scalding insults I try to escape from&lt;br /&gt;
As tears stream out like the warm water above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crying in the shower&lt;br /&gt;
The snakes screaming louder&lt;br /&gt;
My thoughts starting to whirl and my mind beginning to swirl&lt;br /&gt;
“You’ll never be as good as him”&lt;br /&gt;
“Your choices will never get you anywhere”&lt;br /&gt;
“The people you trust will betray one once more”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They wanted a boy, not a girl”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turning off the shower&lt;br /&gt;
Snakes spitting out their last drops of water&lt;br /&gt;
I take my towel and rub the tears from my eyes.&lt;br /&gt;
As I stand before the mirror&lt;br /&gt;
And comb my wet hair&lt;br /&gt;
I say goodbye to my snake family of lies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>CelesteStarlite</name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">October 29th, 2020 Snakes in the Shower A poem about negative voices</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dice</title><link href="/prose/2020/11/30/dice.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dice" /><published>2020-11-30T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-11-30T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>/prose/2020/11/30/dice</id><content type="html" xml:base="/prose/2020/11/30/dice.html">&lt;p&gt;Recently, I stumbled upon an old sheet of paper from years prior. It was a math assignment, but I couldn’t tell what year it was from. It looked like it was ripped from one of those workbooks we were given at the beginning of the year, well before we started getting textbooks that we’d solve problems from on lined paper. The lesson was on probability, but the thing that caught my eye was a handwritten chart, the pencil marks fading away on the thin paper. All it had was the 36 values that 2 6-sided dice could roll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dice had become a big part of my life since then. I started playing tabletop games and I was introduced to Dungeons and Dragons. I ended up buying myself not one, but two sets of dice to carry around as my own. I began playing war simulators, and bought tens of dice to use as counters. Almost daily, I’d roll dice to determine an outcome. To determine if my shots hit the target or if my disguise fooled the guard. How well my sword cut the vines, or how well I understood the lovecraftian scriptures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back then I didn’t understand that the important thing about a dice roll wasn’t what number it rolled. In reality, it was important to decide when to roll my dice. It’s all about maximizing your chances. Rolling dice with bonuses that guarantee your victory, or deciding to flee instead of fighting impossible odds. But most importantly, it’s all about the reward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most important thing to remember is what you’re trying to achieve, and what is at stake. If you roll to see how well you can sneak past highly trained guards just to retrieve a ring you found on the corpse of a goblin from a session ago, there’s a chance you risk your life for something with little value. If you try to cheat at a card game in a bar just to impress your friends when the people you’re against are carrying knives, there’s nothing to truly gain. I didn’t understand this for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day, our school was the target of a threat posted on social media. According to information I received after, there were a couple pictures that made it seem like someone was threatening to bring a gun to school. Because of this, the school said that it was ok for people to skip school due to feeling unsafe. I, however, was planning to go to school. The night before the threat was supposed to be carried out, I didn’t feel worried. In my mind, there was such a little chance that a school shooting would actually occur. There wasn’t anything to worry about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got calls from my brother that my mother was incredibly distraught that I had chosen to go to school. When she came home, she begged me to stay home in case anything happened. I agreed awkwardly, and both my brother and mother took me into a large embrace. It was only then that I began crying, when I realized what I would have done. I didn’t realize how much I was risking just to attend a school day that was optional. Even if there was such a small chance, there was no reason for me to roll the dice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That day I stayed home, lying in bed and letting the day tick by and texting friends back and forth. Nothing happened. In fact, it was later discovered that the guns in the pictures were fake, and had been purchased as props for a music video. That night the anxiety should have faded away, knowing that no shooting truly occured. But fear gripped me tighter. All I could think about was what would have happened if I rolled my dice and turned up snake eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I’ve seen an increase in my skill in tabletop games. Everytime I play, I find that I’ve gotten much better since I started playing. No matter if I’m fighting zombies, trying to survive in a snowstorm, exploring the mystery of a ghost town, or trying to smuggle counterfeit goods into town, I’m finding myself managing to win more and more. But it isn’t because I got lucky all of a sudden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s because I know when to roll my dice.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>CelesteStarlite</name></author><category term="prose" /><summary type="html">Recently, I stumbled upon an old sheet of paper from years prior. It was a math assignment, but I couldn’t tell what year it was from. It looked like it was ripped from one of those workbooks we were given at the beginning of the year, well before we started getting textbooks that we’d solve problems from on lined paper. The lesson was on probability, but the thing that caught my eye was a handwritten chart, the pencil marks fading away on the thin paper. All it had was the 36 values that 2 6-sided dice could roll.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Celeste Introductions</title><link href="/celeste/2020/09/27/introductions.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Celeste Introductions" /><published>2020-09-27T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-09-27T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>/celeste/2020/09/27/introductions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/celeste/2020/09/27/introductions.html">&lt;p&gt;Hi! Um…I’m Celeste!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know much about you, honestly. All I know is that you know about me, although I’m not very certain how much you know about me either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But we can change that! I want you to trust me—after all, if we’ll be working so closely together you should be able to put your faith in me, right? So, let me tell you a bit about myself!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I live with my brother and sister in a tiny house in a small pocket of the world. Nobody can really find us where we are, at least that’s what I’m told. According to my father, he made it so that nobody would come after us. I don’t really understand why anyone would want to hurt us, but my father was always really paranoid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My sister usually takes care of us. She’s the oldest out of the three of us, but my brother still likes to take change when he can. She’s usually the one who accompanies me when I go out anywhere or sanctions my brother’s travels. My brother’s a kind of…lone wolf, I suppose. He’s really kind, I know that, but he doesn’t usually spend much time at home. He’s the only one of us that goes out often, so he’s usually not home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spend a lot of my time at home bored. It’s really hard to find stuff to do, you know? It’s really quiet in the house sometimes, and there’s not much to do outside when my brother is out and my sister is cooking. I’m usually just left laying in the grass, where me and Neb usually relax.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! Nebby is my pet dog! She’s been with us ever since I was born—at least, I can’t remember a time where she wasn’t there. My father told me that I used to never get sleep unless I was resting against her. I don’t blame young me either, Her fur is one of the softest things I’ve ever felt. There’s still nights I cuddle with her so I can sleep after a long day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know father was trying to protect us when he moved here, but I still don’t really get it. I don’t think people really want to hurt us. I mean, I don’t think people are really evil. Sometimes they just don’t understand that what they’re doing is wrong. I’m sure a lot of people do things and regret it afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, I wasn’t going to be kept inside for long. One night that I couldn’t sleep, I followed my brother downstairs to the basement where I found a door hidden behind a sum of boxes. Moving them out of the way, he started to slip through the door. I didn’t follow him immediately—I was really worried he’d notice me, so I snuck back upstairs and hid under my blankets until the sun came back up. After breakfast, I went back downstairs to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never wanted to spend time in the basement. It was always dark and dusty, and every step on the old crooked floorboards would let out a loud, sharp crack that rang through the room. Sneaking over and pushing the boxes to the right, I saw a well kept door that stood out in comparison to the dimly lit, run down underside of the house. A dim light was leaking out of the crack under the door. With a deep breath, I opened the door and left my home for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After I discovered there was more than the little cottage and tree I grew up in, I began to sneak out as often as I could. Weekly, daily, any moment that I could I’d slip past the door in the basement and explore whatever world was on the other side. Every world I went to was different, with different scenery and different people. Sometimes I’d be only a couple minutes. Other times I’d stay for hours, or days. Sometimes weeks or months. Time passed differently in those worlds than it did in mine. I’d leave for ten minutes even if it felt like a year, or I’d leave for what felt like a couple days and weeks could go by. My brother would always yell and my sister would always worry, but nothing stopped me from venturing out to the other worlds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I met lots of interesting people and saw many interesting sights, but the strangest thing to me was the world I couldn’t visit. I heard my brother talk about it sometimes. He’d been visiting every world like crossing them off a list and he found one that just…didn’t work. Circled in red on his wall of notes, there was just one place he could never go to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried myself. I didn’t understand how the door worked, or how to choose where to go, but after enough worlds I found one I just…couldn’t. The door led to a black void—like a computer that hadn’t been turned on. I could feel there was something there, as if I was bumping around a room without the lights on. I desperately tried finding my way, trying to turn on the lights or find the power switch to whatever this world was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s when I found you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure how to make you trust me, but I want you to know I’m not here to hurt you. If anything, I’m here to help you. Hopefully I can explain it all to you in due time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, how about you tell me a bit about yourself?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>CelesteStarlite</name></author><category term="celeste" /><summary type="html">Hi! Um…I’m Celeste!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dream - Part 2 (Redux)</title><link href="/celeste/2020/07/31/dream-pt-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dream - Part 2 (Redux)" /><published>2020-07-31T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-31T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>/celeste/2020/07/31/dream-pt-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="/celeste/2020/07/31/dream-pt-2.html"></content><author><name>CelesteStarlite</name></author><category term="celeste" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dream - Part 1 (Redux)</title><link href="/2020/07/07/dream-pt-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dream - Part 1 (Redux)" /><published>2020-07-07T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-07T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>/2020/07/07/dream-pt-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/07/07/dream-pt-1.html"></content><author><name>CelesteStarlite</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Failure</title><link href="/prose/2020/03/19/failure.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Failure" /><published>2020-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>/prose/2020/03/19/failure</id><content type="html" xml:base="/prose/2020/03/19/failure.html">&lt;p&gt;I have an unabating disdain for failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To spend so much unnecessary time—so many precious hours or even days of my fleeting life just to trip over the finish line. A failure to produce results after countless efforts. An incredible sum of courage and spirit consumed by an inescapable, inevitable void of pain. Every single failure is one more setback that I have only myself to blame for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve realized just how important time is. Any scrap of time that I can salvage is a resource that I can apply to the fleeting life I hold dear, allowing me more action—more freedom of my life that I can feel and take hold of. And to spend so much time—so much important, important time—working towards that freedom for it to be removed is soul crushing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everytime I fail I have the unquenchable urge to try again. Everytime I push once more past the failure and try to salvage the precious time I had spent. I gather up the shards of my mistake and push them together in an effort to hold something in my shaking, beaten hands. I beat my head against the wall, punching and kicking in a futile attempt to break it down and push through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every time, I fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fall down to my knees, confronted with the fact that my time was wasted. I clench my tired hands and scream into a void of pain, piled high with the failures I can’t mend—the embodiment of the time wasted, never to return. The pile of mistakes extends to the heavens, and as I reach ever closer to the void I fail to fathom how deep it goes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sands of time I had piled up to collect fall through my feeble hands and disappear unknowingly into the abyss I stand above. Another pile of trash to add to my past—an endless void full of failures and mistakes. Nothing to salvage, nothing to save, nothing to achieve. An endless nothingness. An insurmountable and overwhelming empty void.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet despite it all, in face of constant never ending failure,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I reach out towards the light that shines bright against the abyss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deterred, unmotivated, crushed, uninspired,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stand once more and trek through the hellish landscape in my mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a neverending spark within my soul, I extend myself towards a fleeting dream impossibly far away, yet close enough to feel within my broken fingers. I stretch out my arm as a feeble yet noble attempt to close the gap that spans past the void around me. I reach out because I know that the light beyond the walls exists. Unlike the void that surrounds my mind, I reach out to a dream that’s within my grasp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The eternal nonexistent fight within my mind wages constantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet I shall stand one more.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>CelesteStarlite</name></author><category term="prose" /><summary type="html">I have an unabating disdain for failure.</summary></entry></feed>